<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PhotonApp</string>
    <string name="large_txt">A Hicksville-based charity formed to honor the memory of a young girl who lost her battle to cancer will combine chuckles and charity for an upcoming fundraiser.

The 14th Annual Night of Laughter benefits children battling pediatric cancer and their families. The event will be held at the Crest Hollow Country Club in Woodbury on Friday, April 14 at 7 p.m.
    Sarah Grace Foundation for Children With Cancer Inc. is named after Sarah Grace Weippert, who lost her battle with Acute Lymphoblastic Leukemia in 2002 at the age of 12. Her parents, Matt and Marissa Weippert founded the organization the following year with the goal of improving the quality of life of children with cancer, and to provide comfort and support to their families.

    “We are grateful to our family, friends and community that have loved and supported our mission for the last 14 years and continue to honor Sarah’s memory,” Matthew Weippert said in a press release. “This event is critical to the advancement of our mission.”

    The event host will be comedian Rick Morgan, who has performed in Atlantic City and at Caroline’s New York City. Morgan is a dedicated supporter of the foundation. “I am overwhelmed by the inspiration this little girl has given me,” he said of Sarah. “I feel like a soldier in her battles and victories.”
    This year’s slate of comedians include:

    Holbrook native Stevie Geebee, “the World’s Funniest Accountant.” He is known for his Long Island specific comedy.
    Jack Simmons, who has appeared on Showtime, HBO and Evening at the Apollo,
    Steve Marshall, who has performed his standup routine at comedy clubs, resorts and colleges across the country.
    Al Martin, seen on the Joan Rivers Show and the Geraldo Show and owner of two Manhattan comedy clubs.
    The night is for mature audiences only. The cost of a ticket is $85 per person and includes entertainment, dinner, beer, wine, soda, coffee and dessert.

    Raffle prizes include four Walt Disney World park passes, TD Bank Visa Gift Cards, as well as a 50/50/50 with even prizes for three winners. Raffle books, which include these grand prizes, are available at a pre-show discount of $25 per book. Tickets for the event and raffle books must be purchased in advance.

    A Chinese auction will include prizes such as restaurant gift certificates, lottery scratch-off tickets, baskets of cheer, a bicycle and more.

    This is traditionally a popular event, so reserve your tickets early by calling (516) 433-9745 or visiting

    </string>
</resources>
